Friends, I welcome you to your own
YouTube channel.  Before starting the video, I would like to
request all of you that if
you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
it is my request to all of you, please subscribe to the channel.
Like
and share the video as much as possible so that
this video can reach as many people as possible.
So let's start.
Where you can see, today we will discuss
about HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank.  There will be
a comparison between these two as to
which bank
is better as per the current results and whose target is coming out,
how are the technicals of both, we are going to
check all these things, so let's
start here, first of all if
HDFC Bank is on this side you can see,
here you have ICICI Bank, check the market cap, you
can see that the market cap of
HDFC Bank is Rs 1548200
crore.  You can see ICICI Bank's
₹987427
crore.  So, there is a huge
gap in the market cap of both.   If you
check the employee then see 26758 here it is
in HDFC Bank.  If you check it, you
can see 128623.  So HDF
is far ahead of ICICI Bank, if you check HDFC Bank branches then
they have 9545 branches.   If you
check out the 7246 ATMs owned by ICICI Bank,
it has 2147 ATMs.  HDFC
Bank has 10610
and now if we check the valuation part, if we
check the PY ratio, then we
can see that it is 13% of the industry.  And if you check HDFC Bank, it is trading at
21.4, which means it is
trading much higher than Industries.  And if you
check ICICI Bank, you can see that it is
18.5.  That means it is expensive as compared to the industry
but if you check with HDFC Bank then it is
seen to be cheaper here.  You
can see.  So you can check the PY ratio here.  That
is, the valuation
part.  Next is your earnings per share.   If we
check the EPS, it is 47.2 of HDFC
Bank.  ICICI Bank has a much higher EPS of 474.9,
which means that ICICI Bank is much better than HDFC Bank. If we
check ICICI Bank's ranking in terms of EPS, then
who is number one?  So HDFC Bank is your
ICICI Bank here in seconds.  If we check in Nifty weightage,
HDFC Bank has 13.11%
and ICICI Bank has
9% in Nifty.  If you check Bank Nifty, it
is at number one with 28.49%,
how much is it?  ACI Bank's share is 24.38%.
Revenue will now move towards results.  So
see, the revenue growth is 4% on yearly basis.
How much is there here?  Of 3%.
That is, whose revenue is growing more
?  So the revenue of HDFC Bank is
growing more.  Now the revenue planet which
we had just checked, this was the first revenue which you had just
checked, this was your
comparison on yearly basis.  Now if we
check on quarterly basis then
see its revenue growth, the revenue growth has
fallen here.  If you compare it with the previous quarter, it is
-1%.  There is a decline.  And ICICI
Bank has fallen more.  We can see -3%, we are
talking about quarterly basis.  If we
check the net profit on yearly basis, there is an
increase of 11%.  There
is a jump of 3% in HDFC Bank here.
HDFC Bank has seen a 3% jump in net profit on a quarterly basis.
And if you check here, a
decline is seen here on quarterly basis.  That means,
if we check the performance profit wise, then the
performance of HDFC Bank is much better.
In terms of revenue and also in terms of profit.  If you
check NI, there is a growth of 5%.  If you
check this, 7% means that the
end net interest income of ICICI Bank is
better in comparison to HDFC Bank.
Next is provisioning, that is, the money
which is a risky amount, so see, 30%,
here a decline is being seen
in HDFC Bank.  But who has more?
So the biggest decline of 35% was
seen here in ICICI Bank.  That means the
provisioning of ICICI Bank has reduced significantly here.  You
can see.  If you check the gross NPO, it has
decreased from 1.36 to 1.24.
But here it decreased from 1.97 to 1.58.
That means who is performing better
?  So of ICICI Bank.  Net NPA
is still 0.42.  Look at it happening here.   It has
decreased from 0.42 to 0.39 and if you check the deposit
then there is a growth of 15%.  There
is a growth of 9.10% here.  So HDFC Bank is better.  Now let's move ahead.
Apart from that, if you check, the
loan growth is 10%.  Here the loan
growth is 10.30%.  KASA is 33.90.
Its value is 39.20.  You can see.  So
in many cases ICI Bank is also ahead.  Capital
ADC 17% Its 17.90% brokerage
is on the positive side.  It was
seen on the mixed side.  Mixed response is being
seen here after the results.
Next is the technical part, we will
check it later.  Its dividend payout is much
better at 25%.  ICICI Bank's 16.60
dividend 1.09%, if you check it from 0.80% and 52 high, it
is currently trading near 52 high.  Correction in the range of 8% to 10% has
already come in this.  Now let's move ahead.
Ah, if you check the technical
part then look at HDFC Bank.  Ah, right now
its price is running in the range of 104.   If you
check,
it is currently trading above both 50 day and 200 moving averages.
That means what is the trend?  There
is a bullish trend.  Well, even
better moves can be seen here.  If you check ICI Bank, the
current
price is ₹1381.  It is below the 50 day moving average and
above the 200 moving average.
That means what is the trend?
Trading in the inexorable zone.  It can go anywhere.
What's up now?  The important support
level is emerging in the range of 200 moving average.  Please pay
attention to this thing.   If it
goes below this then what will be its trade trend
?  There will be a bearish trend.
Now if we check the brokerage report,
HDFC Bank has
fixed the target price of ₹195 for HDFC Bank.
Rated Buy.  Also, if you
check the remaining brokerages, the
average price is ₹149.  That means a
return of up to 14% can come from here.  So
this is the brokerage report about HDFC Bank.
Next is ICICI Bank, if we check it then
ICICI Bank shares fell over 2%
as analyst one of the growth concerns.  So,
concerns are being raised here regarding growth
in ICICI Bank.  Out of these, 51 analysts are
covering ICICI Bank, out of
which 48 have given buy rating and
remaining have given hold rating,
no one has given sell rating here, this is
ICICI Bank, along with this there is one more, here
CLS has maintained all perform
rating,
target price of 1700 has been fixed for ICICI Bank, which is quite
high.  You can see it is quite high.
Burnston has a market perform
fixed price of 1440.  Dam Capital
believes that while the operational
performance for the lender remains stable, the
growth needs more growth. There is a
little bit of concern here.  So a mixed
kind of response is being seen here
from the brokerage side for ICICI Bank.
Now let's move ahead.  Now see, we have done the comparison.
Who has the higher market cap?  So look at HDFC Bank,
I have colored it green here.  Among employees, you
can see that HDFC Bank is ahead.   If you
check HDFC Bank valuation at HDFC Bank ATM in the branch network,
ICICI Bank is better.  So now if you
check out of five, it has four points.
And ICICI Bank's one point is
visible here.  Now let's move ahead.
Also, if you check EPS, you will
see that ICICI Bank is ahead.
This is the number one rank in the ranking.
HDFC Bank has the same weightage in Nifty.  It has a share
in revenue.  So if we
check the total, HDFC Bank got eight points.
Till now ICICI Bank has got two points.
Now let's move ahead.  Next is
revenue growth, if you check it, you
can see that both are negative, hence there is no
point.  Who is ahead in net profit
?  So HDFC Bank Net Profit
on Quarterly Basis, who can see next in HDFC Bank Net Interest
Income, ICICI Bank i.e.
AC Bank has got three points and it has got
10 points till now, which is visible here.
Now let's move ahead.  If you
check the provisioning, you can see that
ICICI Bank has a better preference in provisioning.
ICICI Bank's performance is also better in Gross NPO.
Its performance in net NPA is also better.  But
HDFC Bank's in deposit growth.  So
what is the total?  11 points to HDFC Bank.
You are getting six points for ICICI Bank.
Now let's move ahead.  If you check the loan growth, you will
see that HDFC Bank is at 10%.  Its
performance is much better than ICICI Bank.
ICICI Bank is better in Kasa also.   If we
check the brokerage of ICICI Bank in capital adequacy also, it is
on the positive side.  And what about this?  So it
is mixed.  So HDFC Bank has 12 points.
How much does it have?  Nine Points can be
seen here.  You can see.  Ah, let's move on now.
Apart from that, if you check,
HDFC Bank is ahead in dividend payout.
HDFC Bank also traded near 52% high in dividend yield,
hence I have
kept a bullish trend here.  So the total became 16
points.  It has so many nine points that can still be
seen.  So
now if we check the total, HDFC
Bank has got 16 points.  Axis Bank has
got nine points.  What is the total points
?  So,
HDFC Bank has got 16 points out of 26.  It has got nine
points.  That means HDFC Bank is much higher in
comparison to ICICI Bank in every terms.
What do you say?  Please tell me.  And you
also please tell me whether you should say goodbye to it.
Who is going to buy which bank?  This
was the complete update.  I hope you will also like
, share and subscribe to the channel.  Thank
you.